I've been really trying to formulate how to show compassion to Israelis who have aligned in this
way. He's talking about an IDF soldier. This is under the video of underscore Jennifer Kings
in Times Square talking to IDF soldiers who are saying, oh my god, why are we all the same?
I'm gonna find a solution. I'm not absolving any responsibility, but I do think the secret sauce
is attacking with love and some potent way that gets past the rationalization firewalls. And you
know, I let this live under the comments until today he says, it's worth a shot. They are our
families just as we all are. Shut up, Reggie Watts. Shut up. Should I invite my rapist over and try to
understand his reasoning through love? Or maybe all the families who keep on inviting the PDFs to the
barbecue, maybe that's what they're doing. They're approaching them with love. The instinct to want to
reach out to the harmful, to want to connect with folks who are in no way asking for any type of
understanding, who are not looking for any level of atonement, who are not expressing any type of
remorse, is an incongruity of affect. It is not a response of empathy. What it is, in fact,
is a response of ego. Let me explain. This is the type of nonsense that is harmful to any shift
happening in the world, because instead of putting his energy towards showing love to the
millions of people that have been harmed by Zionists, he's saying, you know what, maybe I can try and flip
them. I can't stand you people. I can't stand you. This is like when Ice Cube was like, I know what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna go talk to Trump and get in the Black Klan. I'll bet you he'll listen to me. I'm Cube.
The ego is the enemy. You know what, Reggie? While you're at it, drop by at Klan meeting.
I'm sure they would love to see you.